TIFFANY BROWN

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/tiffany-brown-7553644a/ 7 /TJBrowne

SUMMARY

I am a former pharmacy technician and college office assistant entering the software development field with a practical foundation in administrative, and organizational skills acquired from broad-based part and full-time work experience. An inquisitive mind interested in optimizing the performance of websites for businesses. Also interested in utilizing my technical and analytical skills to create dynamic websites, and apps to give a company a competitive edge.

EMPLOYMENT

July 2018 to Current General Assembly ⋅ Web Development Immersive ⋅ New York, NY

General Assembly's Web Development Immersive (WDI) is a 12week long training program dedicated to prepare students to think like engineers and approach problems creatively in order to build the next generation of web applications and digital products.

Oct. 2013 to July 2018 CVS Pharmacy · Pharmacy Technician · New York, NY

Processed prescriptions, resolve Third Party rejections and complete any manual claim forms.

Resolved Third Party rejections and complete any manual claim forms.

March 2016 to Oct. 2018 Medgar Evers College CUNY · Buildings & Grounds-College Assistant · Brooklyn, NY

Maintained a variety of records, supplies, calendar, schedules, files, etc. (e.g. employee time reports, fiscal information, work orders,

etc.)

Performed record keeping (confidential and non-confidential) and general and program specific clerical functions (e.g. scheduling,

copying, faxing, etc.).

July 2016 to April 2013 Publix Supermarket · Cashier · Hollywood, FL

Accepted cash, checks, or bankcards for payment; completes check and bankcard transactions according to established procedure.

Assisted in other areas of store, such as clean-up, shelf stocking.

Jan. 2012 to June 2016 Department of Information Technology & Telecommunication · Call Center Representative ·

New York, NY

Answered incoming calls within the 24-hour/7-day/week operations in a professional and courteous manner.

Maintained customer satisfaction; Identify customers' needs and assist accordingly.

Enter call data into a computerized tracking system.

Oct. 2008 to Oct. 2010 Duane Reade Pharmacy · Pharmacy Technician · Brooklyn, NY

Provided support to customers and assisted pharmacists in filling prescriptions and maintaining customer database.

Responded to inquiries from a variety of internal and external parties (in person and by telephone) (e.g. staff, public agencies, etc.)

for the purpose of providing information, facilitating communication among parties.

EDUCATION

July 2018 to Current General Assembly

2018 Certificate Web Development

Aug. 2004 to Feb. 2008 John Jay College of Criminal Justice//CUNY

2010 AA Criminal Justice

Aug. 2013 to June 2016 Medgar Evers College/CUNY

D16 BA Psychology

SKILLS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

HTML & CSS, JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, Node.js

MICROSOFT PowerPoint, Excel

AWARDS

Nov. 2015 Medgar Evers College CUNY · Dean's List Awards

VOLUNTEERING